A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1981-1990 FA402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1983; 0.34 Cubic Feet 26 microfilm reels (35mm); 26 Reels 26 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - Nigeria, 1983; 1983/497
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, 1983; 1983/497.E
      - Ilori, Felicia A. D., 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 736)
  - France, 1983; 1983/500
    - Roussel Uclaf, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 779)
  - French Guinea, 1983; 1983/525
    Guinea
    - Diallo, Cellou, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 845)
  - China, 1983; 1983/601
    - F-Z, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 848)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1983; 1983/601.D
      - Agriculture, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 975)
    - China - Fellowships, 1983; 1983/601.E
      - Chinese Academy of Agriculutral Sciences, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 978)
  - Taiwan, 1983; 1983/605
    - Asian Vegetable Development Center, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 1056)
  - Japan, 1983; 1983/609
    - R-U, 1983 (Reel 25, Frame 1060)
  - Thailand, 1983; 1983/617
    - B-S, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
  - Holland, 1983; 1983/650
    - Muller, A.S., 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 27)
  - Indonesia, 1983; 1983/652
    - Soekanto Lebdosoekojo, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 32)
  - Belgium, 1983; 1983/707
    - European Cultural Foundation, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 39)
  - Belgian Congo, 1983; 1983/709
    - Ngonda Bagonda, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 49)
  - Germany, 1983; 1983/717
    - Max Planck Institute for Immunobiology (Eichmann, Klaus), 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 61)
  - Tanganyika, 1983; 1983/723
    - Education, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 107)
  - Zambia, 1983; 1983/724
    Zambia
    - Zambia (Reel 26)
  - Italy, 1983; 1983/751
    - American People/ American Music Festival, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 166)
    - Italy - Fellowships, 1983; 1983/751.E
      - De Santis, Rosaria, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 418)
  - Poland, 1983; 1983/789
    - Ostrowski, Jan, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 452)
  - Spain, 1983; 1983/795
    Spain
    - Vargus-Machuca, Ramon, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 462)
  - Sweden, 1983; 1983/800
    - B-P, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 467)
  - Turkey, 1983; 1983/805
    - Kagitcibase, Cigdem, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 491)
  - Egypt, 1983/812
    - Egypt - Medical Sciences, 1983; 1983/812.A
      - Suez Canal University (Medical School), 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 518)
  - Members and Meetings, 1983; 1983/903
    - B-W, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 567)
  - Humanities, 1983/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1983; 1983/911.E
      - American Antiquarian Society (Resident Fellows), 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 625)
      - B-K, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 723)
      - L-O, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 978)
      - P-Y, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 1031)
  - Travel, 1983; 1983/917
    - A-T, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 1271)
- General Correspondence, 1984; 0.44 Cubic Feet 33 microfilm reels (35mm); 33 Reels 33 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1984; 1984/100
    - Halstead, Scott B. (Meetings), 1984 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Lyman, Judith M., 1984 (Reel 1, Frame 620)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (Recommendations), 1984 (Reel 1, Frame 846)
    - Segal, Sheldon J., 1984 (Reel 1, Frame 923)
    - A-D, 1984 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - G-J, 1984 (Reel 2, Frame 251)
    - L-P, 1984 (Reel 2, Frame 426)
    - R-W, 1984 (Reel 2, Frame 512)
    - A-W, 1984 (Reel 2, Frame 737)
    - International Centre for Genetic Engneering and Biotechnology, 1984 (Reel 2, Frame 936)
  - International Organizations, 1984; 1984/103
    - International (B-U), 1984 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - United Nations (C-E), 1984 (Reel 3, Frame 729)
    - United Nations (F-W), 1984 (Reel 3, Frame 878)
    - United Nations Development Programme, 1984 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1984 (Reel 4, Frame 277)
    - United Nations University (Institute for Natural Resources in Africa), 1984 (Reel 4, Frame 404)
    - C-V, 1984 (Reel 4, Frame 418)
    - W, 1984 (Reel 4, Frame 707)
    - International Organizations - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1984; 1984/103.D
      - International Society for Plant Molecular Biology, 1984 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture - Nigeria (IITA), 1984; 1984/115
    - Soybean Utilization Pilot Plant, 1984 (Reel 5, Frame 7)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1984; 1984/120
    - A-I, 1984 (Reel 5, Frame 18)
    - K-W, 1984 (Reel 5, Frame 191)
  - Conflict in International Relations, Declinations, 1984; 1984/155
    - E-W, 1984 (Reel 5, Frame 575)
  - Conquest of Hunger - Increasing Food Production, 1984; 1984/165
    - Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel, 1984 (Reel 5, Frame 728)
  - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research, 1984/175
    - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research - Fellowships, 1984; 02.1984/175.E
      - Pinderhughes, Dianne M., 1984 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
  - Special Interests and Explorations - Immigrants, 1984; 1984/181
    - Bodnar, John E., 1984 (Reel 6, Frame 37)
  - Health of Populations (HP)/Health Sciences (HS) - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN), 1984; 1984/197
    - A-Z, 1984 (Reel 6, Frame 70)
  - United States, 1984; 1984/200
    - Ab-Al, 1984 (Reel 6, Frame 295)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (A-R), 1984 (Reel 6, Frame 918)
    - American Association of Museums (Commission on Museums), 1984 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1984 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - American (A-E), 1984 (Reel 8, Frame 161)
    - American Historical Association (History), 1984 (Reel 8, Frame 459)
    - American (L-S), 1984 (Reel 8, Frame 822)
    - Appalshop, Inc. (Appalachia History), 1984 (Reel 8, Frame 1020)
    - Am-At, 1984 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Ba-Bo, 1984 (Reel 9, Frame 553)
    - Br-Bu, 1984 (Reel 9, Frame 882)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, 1984 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Center (A-T), 1984 (Reel 10, Frame 214)
    - Ca-Ch, 1984 (Reel 10, Frame 438)
    - Ci-Cl, 1984 (Reel 10, Frame 892)
    - Coc-Con, 1984 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Council on Foundations (International Grantmaking), 1984 (Reel 11, Frame 390)
    - Coo-Cou, 1984 (Reel 11, Frame 574)
    - Cr-Cu, 1984 (Reel 11, Frame 758)
    - Diversity, 1984 (Reel 11, Frame 912)
    - D, 1984 (Reel 11, Frame 1076)
    - E, 1984 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Food Policy Forum (Videotape), 1984 (Reel 12, Frame 387)
    - F, 1984 (Reel 12, Frame 433)
    - G, 1984 (Reel 12, Frame 739)
    - Harvard University (B-W), 1984 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Houpis, John N., 1984 (Reel 13, Frame 422)
    - H, 1984 (Reel 13, Frame 760)
    - International (C-W), 1984 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - I, 1984 (Reel 14, Frame 378)
    - Johns Hopkins University (B-I), 1984 (Reel 14, Frame 908)
    - Johns Hopkins University Press (Goellner, Jack G.), 1984 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - J, 1984 (Reel 15, Frame 109)
    - K, 1984 (Reel 15, Frame 343)
    - La-Le, 1984 (Reel 15, Frame 716)
    - Li-Lo, 1984 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Ma-Mc, 1984 (Reel 16, Frame 422)
    - Murphy, Fredrick A., 1984 (Reel 16, Frame 926)
    - Me-Mu, 1984 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - National (A), 1984 (Reel 17, Frame 400)
    - National Council for the Humanities, 1984 (Reel 17, Frame 598)
    - National (B-C), 1984 (Reel 17, Frame 673)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (G-S), 1984 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - National (E-F), 1984 (Reel 18, Frame 500)
    - National Research Council (Board on Science and Techonology for International Development, 1984 (Reel 18, Frame 682)
    - National Urban League (G-J), 1984 (Reel 18, Frame 901)
    - National (H-W), 1984 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - New Vaccine Priorities for Developing Countries (Conference), 1984 (Reel 19, Frame 197)
    - New (P-V), 1984 (Reel 19, Frame 309)
    - New York Botanical Garden (Tropical Rain Forest), 1984 (Reel 19, Frame 372)
    - New York City Area Study, 1984 (Reel 19, Frame 432)
    - New York University (A-O), 1984 (Reel 19, Frame 749)
    - New York (C-V), 1984 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - N, 1984 (Reel 20, Frame 155)
    - O, 1984 (Reel 20, Frame 545)
    - P-Pi, 1984 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Purdue University (Hardin, Lowell S.), 1984 (Reel 21, Frame 287)
    - Pl-Pu, 1984 (Reel 21, Frame 497)
    - Rockefeller, 1984 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - Rutgers University (D-W), 1984 (Reel 22, Frame 83)
    - R, 1984 (Reel 22, Frame 362)
    - S-Sm, 1984 (Reel 22, Frame 914)
    - Stakman, Elvin C. (Biography), 1984 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Stanford University (Sowell, Thomas), 1984 (Reel 23, Frame 130)
    - Stanford University, Sowell, Thomas (Supplementary Material), 1984 (Reel 23, Frame 148)
    - Stanford University (C-W), 1984 (Reel 23, Frame 464)
    - So-Sz, 1984 (Reel 23, Frame 581)
    - T, 1984 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - United States (A-T), 1984 (Reel 24, Frame 562)
    - University of California (A-V), 1984 (Reel 24, Frame 777)
    - University (A-D), 1984 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - University (F-I), 1984 (Reel 25, Frame 316)
    - University of Michigan (G-S), 1984 (Reel 25, Frame 593)
    - University of Missouri (C-G), 1984 (Reel 25, Frame 842)
    - University (M), 1984 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - University (N-P), 1984 (Reel 26, Frame 447)
    - University (S-W), 1984 (Reel 26, Frame 762)
    - U-V, 1984 (Reel 26, Frame 1011)
    - WNET/Thirteen (T), 1984 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - W-We, 1984 (Reel 27, Frame 301)
    - Wh-Wi, 1984 (Reel 27, Frame 686)
    - Wo-Wr, 1984 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - Yale University (Black Periodical Fiction Project), 1984 (Reel 28, Frame 557)
    - Yale University (A-W), 1984 (Reel 28, Frame 1078)
    - Y-Z, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - United States - Fellowships, 1984; 1984/200.E
      - B-S, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 160)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1984; 1984/200.R
      - N-Y, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 508)
  - Philippines, 1984; 1984/242
    - G-U, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 522)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1984; 1984/242.D
      - Rice (Genetic Materials Diffusion), 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 652)
  - Puerto Rico, 1984; 1984/243
    - I-U, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 668)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1984; 1984/272
    - D-S, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 681)
  - South America and Latin America, 1984; 1984/300
    South America; Latin America
    - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 696)
    - South America and Latin America - Medical Sciences, 1984; 1984/300.A
      - P-T, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 700)
  - Argentina, 1984; 1984/301
    - Argentina, Medical Research (Abeledo, Carlos), 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 961)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1984; 1984/301.D
      - Agriculture, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 963)
  - Bolivia, 1984; 1984/303
    - Cesar Justineano, Mario, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 1101)
  - Brazil, 1984; 1984/305
    - A-U, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 1104)
  - Chile, 1984; 1984/309
    - Vidaurre Valdes, Alfredo F., 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 1152)
  - Colombia, 1984; 1984/311
    - A-U, 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1984; 1984/311.A
      - University of Antioquia (Medical School), 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 48)
  - Costa Rica, 1984; 1984/313
    - T-U, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 52)
  - Honduras, 1984; 1984/321
    - Cisne, Luis H., 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 125)
  - Mexico, 1984; 1984/323
    - C-U, 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 136)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1984; 1984/323.A
      - Mexico (Ministry of Health), 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 307)
  - Nicaragua, 1984; 1984/325
    Nicaragua
    - Castellon, Paulino, 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 313)
  - England, 1984; 1984/401
    - A-W, 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 316)
    - England - Fellowships, 1984; 1984/401.E
      - Shipton, Parker M., 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 835)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1984; 1984/401.S
      Social sciences
      - Royal Institute of International Affairs (Soviet Foreign Policy), 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 862)
  - Ireland, 1984; 1984/403
    - Martin, Samuel J., 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 871)
  - Scotland, 1984; 1984/405
    Scotland
    - K-U, 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 908)
  - Australia, 1984; 1984/410
    - A-U, 1984 (Reel 30, Frame 1084)
  - Canada, 1984; 1984/427
    - A-U, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
  - Bahamas, 1984; 1984/433
    - Eldon, Reverend Michael, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 245)
  - Hong Kong, 1984; 1984/463
    - University of Hong Kong (Boyde, T.R.C.), 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 247)
  - India, 1984; 1984/464
    - A-R, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 250)
  - Malaysia, 1984; 1984/473
    - F-S, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 339)
  - Nepal, 1984; 1984/474
    - Acharya, Gopal P., 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 432)
  - Kenya, 1984; 1984/476
    - A-W, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 455)
  - South Africa Region, 1984; 1984/487
    - Foundation for Education with Production, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 483)
  - Republic of South Africa, 1984; 1984/489
    - Dali, Chris, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 488)
  - Uganda, 1984; 1984/492
    - Makerere University (Books), 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 507)
  - West Africa Region, 1984; 1984/495
    - I-W, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 516)
  - Nigeria, 1984; 1984/497
    - D-N, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 728)
  - Sierra Leone, 1984/499
    - Sierra Leone - Fellowships, 1984; 1984/499.E
      - Kandeh, H. Borbor Sama, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 796)
  - France, 1984; 1984/500
    - C-S, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 891)
  - People's Republic of China, 1984; 1984/601
    - B-Z, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 930)
    - People's Republic of China - Fellowships, 1984; 1984/601.E
      - Chinese Academy of Agricultural Sciences, 1984 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
  - Taiwan, 1984; 1984/605
    - Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 3)
  - Japan, 1984; 1984/609
    - Nishihara, Masashi, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 8)
    - Nishihara, Masashi (Supplementary Material), 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 27)
    - N-T, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 328)
  - Korea, 1984; 1984/613
    - K, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 372)
  - Thailand, 1984; 1984/617
    - D-U, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 435)
    - Thailand - Undulant Fever, 1984; 1984/617.P
      Brucellosis
      - Sudsawat, Dissarojana, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 469)
  - Holland, 1984; 1984/650
    - E-W, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 559)
  - Indonesia, 1984; 1984/652
    - B-D, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 579)
  - Zaire, 1984; 1984/709
    - Zaire (Reel 32)
  - Germany, 1984; 1984/717
    - D-E, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 631)
  - Tanzania, 1984; 1984/723
    - E-U, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 639)
  - Zambia, 1984; 1984/724
    - International Association for the Advancement of Women in Africa (Hagen, Anthony), 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 703)
  - Greece, 1984; 1984/749
    - Antzoulatou-Retsila, Eurydice, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 720)
  - Hungary, 1984; 1984/750
    Hungary
    - National Institute of Hygiene (Budapest), 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 723)
  - Italy, 1984; 1984/751
    - B-C, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 761)
  - Portugal, 1984; 1984/773
    - Universidade De Coimbra, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 785)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR), 1984; 1984/785
    Soviet Union
    - Arbatov, Georgi, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 788)
  - Finland, 1984; 1984/787
    Finland
    - Lukainen, Tapani, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 792)
  - Sweden, 1984; 1984/800
    - B-P, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 810)
  - Israel, 1984; 1984/825
    - B-W, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 823)
  - Lebanon, 1984; 1984/833
    - American University of Beirut (Kerr, Malcolm), 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 1144)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE) - Biotechnology Career Fellowships, 1984; 1984/860
    - G-P, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 1148)
  - Members and Meetings, 1984; 1984/903
    - E-W, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 1158)
  - Humanities, 1984/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1984; 1984/911.E
      - A-H, 1984 (Reel 32, Frame 1201)
      - I-N, 1984 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
      - R-Y, 1984 (Reel 33, Frame 220)
- General Correspondence, 1985; 0.41 Cubic Feet 31 microfilm reels (35mm); 31 Reels 31 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1985; 1985/100
    - Halstead, Scott B. (Meetings), 1985 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Lyman, Richard W., 1985 (Reel 1, Frame 906)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (Recommendations), 1985 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - A-K, 1985 (Reel 2, Frame 131)
    - L-W, 1985 (Reel 2, Frame 683)
  - International Organizations, 1985; 1985/103
    - International Congress for Infectious Diseases, 1985 (Reel 2, Frame 1040)
    - Task Force for Child Survival (Meeting), 1985 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - United Nations (D-W), 1985 (Reel 3, Frame 42)
    - United Nations Development Programme (M-R), 1985 (Reel 3, Frame 89)
    - United Nations International Development Organization (Cooke, James S.), 1985 (Reel 3, Frame 159)
    - United Nations University (Institute for Natural Resources in Africa), 1985 (Reel 3, Frame 163)
    - C-E, 1985 (Reel 3, Frame 243)
    - I, 1985 (Reel 3, Frame 557)
    - M-W, 1985 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
  - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT), 1985; 1985/105
    - Renfro, Bobby L., 1985 (Reel 4, Frame 519)
  - International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT), 1985; 1985/110
    - Seed Unit, 1985 (Reel 4, Frame 522)
  - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), 1985; 1985/116
    - Lee, Keuk-Ki, 1985 (Reel 4, Frame 656)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1985; 1985/120
    - Miller, Nancy K., 1985 (Reel 4, Frame 661)
    - C-W, 1985 (Reel 4, Frame 679)
  - Inactive Grant Requests, 1985; 1985/121
    - B-N, 1985 (Reel 4, Frame 1086)
  - Conflict in International Relations, Declinations, 1985; 1985/155
    - C-S, 1985 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - Conflict in International Relations, Declinations - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/155.E
      - Reich, Walter, 1985 (Reel 5, Frame 320)
  - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research, 1985/175
    - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/175.E
      - A-S, 1985 (Reel 5, Frame 420)
  - Special Interests and Explorations - Immigrants, 1985; 1985/181
    - Johns Hopkins University (Immigration Corporation), 1985 (Reel 5, Frame 570)
  - Special Interests and Explorations - Family and Women, 1985; 1985/188
    - M-S, 1985 (Reel 5, Frame 605)
  - Health of Populations (HP)/Health Sciences (HS) - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN), 1985; 1985/197
    - A-Z, 1985 (Reel 5, Frame 895)
  - United States, 1985; 1985/200
    - American (A-H), 1985 (Reel 5, Frame 895)
    - American (R-S), 1985 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Ab-Am, 1985 (Reel 6, Frame 61)
    - An-Au, 1985 (Reel 6, Frame 682)
    - Ba-Be, 1985 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Bi-Bu, 1985 (Reel 7, Frame 307)
    - C-Ca, 1985 (Reel 7, Frame 734)
    - Ce-Ch, 1985 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - City University of New York (B-N), 1985 (Reel 8, Frame 542)
    - Ci-Cl, 1985 (Reel 8, Frame 694)
    - Coleman Memorial, 1985 (Reel 8, Frame 788)
    - Constitutional Rights Foundation (Clark, Todd), 1985 (Reel 8, Frame 896)
    - Council on Foundations (International Education Roundtable), 1985 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Council (B-S), 1985 (Reel 9, Frame 210)
    - Co, 1985 (Reel 9, Frame 346)
    - Cr-Cy, 1985 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Danforth Foundation (International Education Roundtable), 1985 (Reel 10, Frame 169)
    - Dinning/Mahidol Proposal, 1985 (Reel 10, Frame 506)
    - D, 1985 (Reel 10, Frame 540)
    - Emory University (C-S), 1985 (Reel 10, Frame 868)
    - E, 1985 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Ford Foundation (A-T), 1985 (Reel 11, Frame 477)
    - Foundation for Biomedical Research, 1985 (Reel 11, Frame 766)
    - F, 1985 (Reel 11, Frame 838)
    - Grantmakers in Health, 1985 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - G, 1985 (Reel 12, Frame 32)
    - Harvard University (D-W), 1985 (Reel 12, Frame 282)
    - H, 1985 (Reel 12, Frame 445)
    - Institute of the Americas, 1985 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Issaquah Health Research Institute, 1985 (Reel 13, Frame 982)
    - I, 1985 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - J, 1985 (Reel 14, Frame 499)
    - K, 1985 (Reel 14, Frame 674)
    - Los Angeles Theatre Center (E-M), 1985 (Reel 14, Frame 928)
    - L, 1985 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Ma-Me, 1985 (Reel 15, Frame 510)
    - Me-Mi, 1985 (Reel 15, Frame 885)
    - Mo-Mu, 1985 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - National (A-G), 1985 (Reel 16, Frame 366)
    - National (H-W), 1985 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Na, 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - New Jersey Consortium for Global Education, 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 74)
    - New (A-W), 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 249)
    - New York Botanical Garden (Institute of Economic Botany), 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 363)
    - New York Public Library (Gregorian, Varton), 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 656)
    - New York (A-S), 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 780)
    - New York University (D-J), 1985 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Ne-No, 1985 (Reel 19, Frame 369)
    - Ohio State University (C-T), 1985 (Reel 19, Frame 508)
    - O, 1985 (Reel 19, Frame 767)
    - Pa-Po, 1985 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - President's Committee on the Arts and Humanitites, 1985 (Reel 20, Frame 593)
    - Pritech Project, 1985 (Reel 20, Frame 738)
    - Pr-Pu, 1985 (Reel 20, Frame 895)
    - R, 1985 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Salk Institute for Biological Studies, 1985 (Reel 21, Frame 446)
    - Salzburg Seminar (European-American Relations), 1985 (Reel 21, Frame 635)
    - S-Sm, 1985 (Reel 21, Frame 944)
    - Sn-Sp, 1985 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - St-Sz, 1985 (Reel 22, Frame 518)
    - T, 1985 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (Cooperative Agreements), 1985 (Reel 23, Frame 432)
    - United States (A-S), 1985 (Reel 23, Frame 608)
    - United States Institute of Peace, 1985 (Reel 23, Frame 809)
    - University Of Alabama (Nutrition), 1985 (Reel 23, Frame 915)
    - University of California (Teachers and Textbooks), 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - University of California (C-T), 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 519)
    - University (A-H), 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 798)
    - University (K-M), 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 911)
    - University (N-P), 1985 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - University (S-W), 1985 (Reel 25, Frame 431)
    - U, 1985 (Reel 25, Frame 769)
    - V, 1985 (Reel 25, Frame 937)
    - Wilson International Center for Scholars (Institute for Media Studies), 1985 (Reel 25, Frame 1024)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1985; 1985/200.A
      - Harvard University, 1985 (Reel 26, Frame 1063)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1985; 1985/200.D
      - T-W, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - United States - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/200.E
      - D-F, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 173)
  - Philippines, 1985; 1985/242
    - B-U, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 258)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1985; 1985/242.D
      - H-R, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 293)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1985; 1985/272
    - A-S, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 403)
  - South America, 1985/300
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1985; 1985/300.A
      - Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 625)
  - Argentina, 1985; 1985/301
    - E-I, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 632)
  - Brazil, 1985; 1985/305
    - C-U, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 702)
  - Chile, 1985; 1985/309
    - U, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 775)
  - Colombia, 1985; 1985/311
    - G-R, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 841)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/311.E
      - Nunez, Zarantes, Victor M., 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 883)
  - Costa Rica, 1985; 1985/313
    - M-U, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 888)
  - Cuba, 1985; 1985/315
    Cuba
    - Cuban Society of Biology of Reporduction and Andrology, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 897)
  - Mexico, 1985; 1985/323
    - A-U, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 900)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1985; 1985/323.A
      - Instituto Mexicano del Seguro Social, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 970)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/323.E
      - Wong, Rebecca, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 973)
  - Peru, 1985; 1985/331
    - Lerner F., Salomon, 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 993)
  - Venezuela, 1985; 1985/339
    - Matos V., Cecilia M., 1985 (Reel 27, Frame 998)
  - England, 1985; 1985/401
    - University of Southampton (C-H), 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - C-W, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 134)
  - Scotland, 1985; 1985/405
    - B-U, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 450)
  - Wales, 1985; 1985/407
    Wales
    - University College of North Wales (Rice Research), 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 471)